<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

  <MaxHitPoints.label>maks. livspoint</MaxHitPoints.label>
  <MaxHitPoints.description>Et objekts maksimale livspoint. Dette repræsenterer hvor meget skade, objektet kan modstå, før det går i stykker.</MaxHitPoints.description>

  <Mass.label>masse</Mass.label>
  <Mass.description>Den fysiske masse af et objekt.</Mass.description>
  <Mass.formatString>{0} kg</Mass.formatString>

  <MarketValue.label>markedsværdi</MarketValue.label>
  <MarketValue.description>Et objekts markedsværdi. Den faktiske salgspris  The actual trade price will be adjusted by negotiation skill, relationship status, and other contextual factors.</MarketValue.description>
  <MarketValue.formatString>${0}</MarketValue.formatString>

  <SellPriceFactor.label>sell price multiplier</SellPriceFactor.label>
  <SellPriceFactor.description>A multiplier on the price at which you can sell items.</SellPriceFactor.description>

  <Flammability.label>brandbarhed</Flammability.label>
  <Flammability.description>Hvor nemt et objekt How easily an object catches fire and how quickly a fire will grow as it burns.</Flammability.description>

  <WorkToMake.label>arbejdsmængde at lave</WorkToMake.label>
  <WorkToMake.description>The base amount of work it takes to make an item, once all materials are gathered.</WorkToMake.description>

  <DeteriorationRate.label>deterioration rate</DeteriorationRate.label>
  <DeteriorationRate.description>The rate at which this item deteriorates when left outside, in average hit points of damage per day. Deterioration rate is also affected by things like weather, roofs, toxic fallout, or being left in shallow water.</DeteriorationRate.description>
  <DeteriorationRate.formatString>{0} / day</DeteriorationRate.formatString>

  <Beauty.label>skønhed</Beauty.label>
  <Beauty.description>How enjoyable an object is to look at. Smukke objekter opfylder en karakters behov for skønhed.</Beauty.description>

  <Cleanliness.label>renlighed</Cleanliness.label>
  <Cleanliness.description>How much an object contributes to an area's cleanliness score.</Cleanliness.description>

  <Comfort.label>komfort</Comfort.label>
  <Comfort.description>Hvor komfortabel et objekt er at sidde eller ligge på. Anvendelsen af komfortable objekter opfylder en karakters behov for komfort.</Comfort.description>

  <Nutrition.label>nutrition</Nutrition.label>
  <Nutrition.description>How nutritious this food is.</Nutrition.description>

  <FoodPoisonChanceFixedHuman.label>madforgiftningschance</FoodPoisonChanceFixedHuman.label>
  <FoodPoisonChanceFixedHuman.description>Chancen for at denne madvare vil resultere i madforgiftning.</FoodPoisonChanceFixedHuman.description>

  <ShootingAccuracyTurret.label>shooting accuracy</ShootingAccuracyTurret.label>
  <ShootingAccuracyTurret.description>Base chance to not miss per cell of shot distance. Chance to hit is also affected by many other factors. A hit chance explanation for any shot can be seen by selecting a shooter and mousing over a target.</ShootingAccuracyTurret.description>


</LanguageData>