<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Tier 1: pre-electricity -->

  <Pemmican.label>pemmikan</Pemmican.label>
  <Pemmican.description>Lav pemmican, en præserveret kombination af kød og planteføde der ikke bliver dårligt i lang tid. Egner sig godt til, når man vil rejse.</Pemmican.description>

  <PassiveCooler.label>passive køler</PassiveCooler.label>
  <PassiveCooler.description>Lav passive kølere, en måde at nedkøle indendørsområder uden elektricitet.</PassiveCooler.description>

  <Brewing.label>Bryggeri</Brewing.label>  
  <Brewing.description>Gør at du kan bygge et bryggeri til at transformere humle til lækker, smagfuld øl.</Brewing.description>

  <Stonecutting.label>stenhugning</Stonecutting.label>
  <Stonecutting.description>Byg stenhuggerborde, der giver mulighed for at forvandle stenklumper til stenblokke, som kan bruges til konstruktion.</Stonecutting.description>

</LanguageData>

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

  <!--===== Column 1 ====-->

  <PsychoidBrewing.label>psychoid brewing</PsychoidBrewing.label>
  <PsychoidBrewing.description>Prepare psychoid leaves into a mildly euphoria-inducing and addictive tea at the campfire or cooking stove.</PsychoidBrewing.description>

  <TreeSowing.label>tree sowing</TreeSowing.label>
  <TreeSowing.description>Sow the local biome's natural trees in your fields.</TreeSowing.description>

  <Brewing.label>ølbrygning</Brewing.label>
  <Brewing.description>Byg et bryggeri og ------------ Build a brewery and fermenting vats to transform hops into tasty, tasty beer.</Brewing.description>

  <ComplexFurniture.label>komplekse møbler</ComplexFurniture.label>
  <ComplexFurniture.description>Byg komplekse møbler som senge, borde, spiseborde, spisestole, lænestole, kommoder, værktøjsskabe, billardborde, pokerborde, udluftningsskakte, sarkofager og meget mere.</ComplexFurniture.description>

  <PassiveCooler.label>passive cooler</PassiveCooler.label>
  <PassiveCooler.description>Make passive coolers, to cool indoor spaces without using electricity.</PassiveCooler.description>

  <Stonecutting.label>stonecutting</Stonecutting.label>
  <Stonecutting.description>Cut rock chunks into stone blocks for use in construction. Build beautiful stone tile floors or ugly concrete walkways.</Stonecutting.description>

  <ComplexClothing.label>komplekst tøj</ComplexClothing.label>
  <ComplexClothing.description>Sy kompleks beklædning såsom bukser, dusters og cowboyhatte.</ComplexClothing.description>


  <!--====== Column 2 ======-->

  <DrugProduction.label>drug production</DrugProduction.label>
  <DrugProduction.description>Build a drug lab for basic drug synthesis. Further research is required to make specific drugs.</DrugProduction.description>

  <Cocoa.label>kakao</Cocoa.label>
  <Cocoa.description>Sow cocoa trees to create your own delicious chocolate. Eating chocolate fulfills the need for recreation, and it's valuable on the market too.</Cocoa.description>

  <Devilstrand.label>devilstrand</Devilstrand.label>
  <Devilstrand.description>Plant devilstrand, a slow-growing mushroom that yields an exceptionally tough, heat-resistant plant fiber.</Devilstrand.description>

  <CarpetMaking.label>carpet making</CarpetMaking.label>
  <CarpetMaking.description>Weave beautiful carpets from cloth.</CarpetMaking.description>

  <Pemmican.label>pemmikan</Pemmican.label>
  <Pemmican.description>Make pemmican, a preserved mixture of meat and plant matter that doesn't go bad for a long time. Great for traveling.</Pemmican.description>


  <!--====== Column 3+ ======-->

  <Smithing.label>smedning</Smithing.label>
  <Smithing.description>Byg smedjer til at lave metalvåben såsom knive, gladii og morgenstjerner. Bearbejd metal til rene, flotte gulvfliser.</Smithing.description>

  <RecurveBow.label>recurvebue</RecurveBow.label>
  <RecurveBow.description>Lav en recurvebue; et effektivt og billigt langdistancevåben.</RecurveBow.description>


  <!--====== Drugs ======-->

  <PsychiteRefining.label>psychite refining</PsychiteRefining.label>
  <PsychiteRefining.description>Refine psychoid leaves into flake and yayo, different forms of the euphoric psychite drug.</PsychiteRefining.description>

  <WakeUpProduction.label>wake-up production</WakeUpProduction.label>
  <WakeUpProduction.description>Synthesize wake-up, a work performance-enhancing drug which replaces the need for sleep.</WakeUpProduction.description>

  <GoJuiceProduction.label>go-juice production</GoJuiceProduction.label>
  <GoJuiceProduction.description>Produce go-juice, a synthetic combat-performance-enhancing drug which improves shooting, melee, and movement ability, and dulls pain.</GoJuiceProduction.description>

  <PenoxycylineProduction.label>penoxycyline production</PenoxycylineProduction.label>
  <PenoxycylineProduction.description>Produce penoxycline, a disease prevention drug which blocks plague, malaria, and more before they start.</PenoxycylineProduction.description>


  <!--====== Medieval weapons ======-->

  <LongBlades.label>long blades</LongBlades.label>
  <LongBlades.description>Lav langsværd og spyd.</LongBlades.description>

  <PlateArmor.label>plate armor</PlateArmor.label>
  <PlateArmor.description>Smith suits of plate armor from metal or wood. This heavy armor noticeably slows movement, but protects very effectively.</PlateArmor.description>

  <Greatbow.label>langbue</Greatbow.label>
  <Greatbow.description>Lav langbuer til at dræbe fjender på lang afstand.</Greatbow.description>


</LanguageData>